<releases>
    <release>
    <date>2015-11-14</date>
    <changes>
      <change>
        <title><![CDATA[Professional Services Schedule Consolidation]]></title>
        <number>0</number>
        <system>eOffer/eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>To ease procurement of professional services, all professional service schedules have been consolidated under the new Professional Services Schedule on October 1st.  The following GSA schedules have been consolidated into the new Professional Services Schedule on October 1st:</p><ul><li>MOBIS Schedule 874</li><li>PES Schedule 871</li><li>FABS Schedule 520</li><li>AIMS Schedule 541</li><li>LOGWORLD Schedule 874 V</li><li>Environmental Schedule 899</li><li>Language Schedule 738 II</li></ul>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Since the changes have taken place on October 1st, no action is needed by vendors since the change will be managed via a unilateral MassMod.</p><p>You can learn more about the Professional Services Schedule (PSS) on the <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/professionalservicescategory">Professional Service Category Community</a> on <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/">Interact</a> or the PSS portal page, <a href="http://www.gsa.gov/portal/content/200063">Professional Service Schedule</a>.</p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
      <change>
        <title><![CDATA[Updated &ldquo;Help&rdquo; Links Throughout eOffer/eMod]]></title>
        <number>1</number>
        <system>eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>A new improved help center has been developed to assist users with eOffer/eMod.  The links throughout eOffer/eMod have been updated to remove old help content and send users to the new site.  </p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>View the new <a href="http://eoffer.gsa.gov/AMSupport/index.html">eOffer/eMod Help Center</a>.</p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
      <change>
        <title><![CDATA[SIN Deletions Now Go Into Effect Immediately]]></title>
        <number>2</number>
        <system>eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Due to a policy change, a Delete SIN modification will go into effect immediately.</p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Vendors should be aware that Delete SIN modifications are effective immediately. 
</p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
    </changes>
  </release>
    <release>
    <date>2015-08-08</date>
    <changes>
      <change>
        <title>Auto-split for Bundled Instantly Effective Price Reduction Modifications</title>
        <number>0</number>
        <system>eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>As of May 2015, temporary price reduction modifications and permanent price reduction modifications were enhanced to become effective immediate.  This includes the following mods:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customers)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Requested)</li></ul><p>However when these modifications were submitted with other modifications that were not designed to go into effect immediately, Contracting Officers had to manually separate these modifications.</p><p>The temporary and permanent price reduction modifications will not be automatically separated by eMod and will go into effect immediately.</p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>You should be aware that the following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customers)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Requested)</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
    </changes>
  </release>
  <release>
    <date>2015-05-09</date>
    <changes>
      <change>
        <title>Technical Proposal Creation in eOffer</title>
        <number>0</number>
        <system>eOffer</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>As a part of the eOffer, vendors have to submit a technical proposal, covering topics such as corporate experience, past performance, and quality control.  Prior to this update, vendors would have to compile this information in a separate document, and attach it to their offers.</p><p>GSA took the opportunity to standardize and streamline the process across the MAS program by creating electronic forms within the eOffer system.  This new robust format allows for increased simplicity, while preserving the commodity-specific elements of certain schedules/SINs.</p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>During the course of 2015, each solicitation in eOffer will include a new section, titled  &ldquo;solicitations provisions&rdquo;.  In this section, offerors will address provisions specific to each solicitation, and provide written detail about their corporate experience, past performance, and quality control.</p><p>Requirements of each section of the provisions are listed with the corresponding text entry boxes.  This ensures consistency and completeness from the vendors.  You must respond to all provisions listed in the table, before you may submit your offer.</p><p>The result is a more user-friendly system and standardized eOffer that Contracting Officers can process more efficiently. </p><p>More information on the Solicitation Provisions process can be found in the <em>eOffer Help Center</em>.</p>]]></description>
          <images>
            <image>
              <url>screenshots/1505/BCR57864_01.jpg</url>
              <caption><![CDATA[Vendors will now enter their technical proposals throught he Solicitation Provisions section of eOffer.]]></caption>
              <alternateText><![CDATA[Vendors will now enter their technical proposals throught he Solicitation Provisions section of eOffer.]]></alternateText>
            </image>
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
      <change>
        <title>Price Reduction Modifications Now Take Effect Upon Submission</title>
        <number>1</number>
        <system>eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>In the past, vendors submitting temporary or permanent price reduction modifications would need to wait for the Contracting Officer to approve the  modification before the modification took effect.  In order to better suit the needs of industry, the process needed to be streamlined.  Therefore, it was decided that price reduction modifications would be effective immediately upon submission.</p>]]></description>          
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>The following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customer)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Request)</li></ul><p>In submitting these modifications, you are now required to agree to the following statements:</p><ul><li>This modification is allowed ONLY to reflect price reductions to be applied to the awarded items under my Multiple Award Schedule contract.  No other changes can be included, and all other contract terms and conditions remain in full effect.</li><li>Submitted price reduction modifications are effective immediately upon submission.</li><li>I must update my Authorized Federal Supply Schedule Price List as soon as possible to reflect the price reductions described herein.</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description>
          <images>
            <image>
              <url>screenshots/1505/BCR69361_01.jpg</url>
              <caption><![CDATA[Price reduction mods will now go into effect upon submission.]]></caption>
              <alternateText><![CDATA[Price reduction mods will now go into effect upon submission.]]></alternateText>
            </image>
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
    </changes>
  </release>
</releases>