<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>eOffer/eMod Release Notes</title><description>The latest release notes for eOffer and eMod.</description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes/releases.rss</link><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:09:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Technical Proposal Required for Add SIN Mod Type]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Vendors are now required to enter a technical proposal via the on-screen entry as part of submitting an “Add SIN” modification. If you submitted a technical proposal as part of your offer, then the content you submitted will be prepopulated and presented for your review. If you did not submit a technical proposal as part of your offer, then you will need to address the required elements as part of completing the modification.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Industrial Funding Fee (IFF) POC Field]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that the <em>Industrial Funding Fee POC</em> is now a mandatory POC for all offers, and that multiple entries are permitted. Existing vendors can add this Point of Contact with a modification.</p> <p>Note that this POC will be pre-populated with the information of the person listed as the 72A POC; you will need to validate this information. In addition, these new POCs may need their own digital certificates. </p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Formatted Product Tool Process]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The Formatted Product Tool will be rolled out to select schedules over the course of the next few months. Contract holders under affected schedules will receive a mass mod. If you are part of an affected schedule, you will receive a mass mod. Upon accepting the mass mod, you will have access to the new process, and will be able to enter detailed pricing information for each of your products and accessories, including discounts, warranties, delivery options, and more. The tool also streamlines multiple sections of eOffer/eMod.</p> <p>You will find both interactive training and step-by-step instructions on the Formatted Product Tool in the eOffer/eMod User Guide.</p> <p>Information about the Formatted Product Tool rollout can be found on the MAS Interact group located at: <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules">https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 21:55:14 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Professional Services Schedule Consolidation]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Since the changes have taken place on October 1st, no action is needed by vendors since the change will be managed via a unilateral MassMod.</p><p>You can learn more about the Professional Services Schedule (PSS) on the <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/professionalservicescategory">Professional Service Category Community</a> on <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/">Interact</a> or the PSS portal page, <a href="http://www.gsa.gov/portal/content/200063">Professional Service Schedule</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Updated &ldquo;Help&rdquo; Links Throughout eOffer/eMod]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>View the new <a href="http://eoffer.gsa.gov/AMSupport/index.html">eOffer/eMod Help Center</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SIN Deletions Now Go Into Effect Immediately]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Vendors should be aware that Delete SIN modifications are effective immediately. </p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Auto-split for Bundled Instantly Effective Price Reduction Modifications]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>You should be aware that the following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customers)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Requested)</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Technical Proposal Creation in eOffer]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>During the course of 2015, each solicitation in eOffer will include a new section, titled &ldquo;solicitations provisions&rdquo;. In this section, offerors will address provisions specific to each solicitation, and provide written detail about their corporate experience, past performance, and quality control.</p><p>Requirements of each section of the provisions are listed with the corresponding text entry boxes. This ensures consistency and completeness from the vendors. You must respond to all provisions listed in the table, before you may submit your offer.</p><p>The result is a more user-friendly system and standardized eOffer that Contracting Officers can process more efficiently. </p><p>More information on the Solicitation Provisions process can be found in the <em>eOffer Help Center</em>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Price Reduction Modifications Now Take Effect Upon Submission]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customer)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Request)</li></ul><p>In submitting these modifications, you are now required to agree to the following statements:</p><ul><li>This modification is allowed ONLY to reflect price reductions to be applied to the awarded items under my Multiple Award Schedule contract. No other changes can be included, and all other contract terms and conditions remain in full effect.</li><li>Submitted price reduction modifications are effective immediately upon submission.</li><li>I must update my Authorized Federal Supply Schedule Price List as soon as possible to reflect the price reductions described herein.</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>