<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>eOffer/eMod Release Notes</title><description>The latest release notes for eOffer and eMod.</description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes/releases.rss</link><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:09:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Technical Proposal Required for Add SIN Mod Type]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Vendors are now required to enter a technical proposal via the on-screen entry as part of submitting an “Add SIN” modification. If you submitted a technical proposal as part of your offer, then the content you submitted will be prepopulated and presented for your review. If you did not submit a technical proposal as part of your offer, then you will need to address the required elements as part of completing the modification.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Industrial Funding Fee (IFF) POC Field]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that the <em>Industrial Funding Fee POC</em> is now a mandatory POC for all offers, and that multiple entries are permitted. Existing vendors can add this Point of Contact with a modification.</p> <p>Note that this POC will be pre-populated with the information of the person listed as the 72A POC; you will need to validate this information. In addition, these new POCs may need their own digital certificates. </p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Formatted Product Tool Process]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The Formatted Product Tool will be rolled out to select schedules over the course of the next few months. Contract holders under affected schedules will receive a mass mod. If you are part of an affected schedule, you will receive a mass mod. Upon accepting the mass mod, you will have access to the new process, and will be able to enter detailed pricing information for each of your products and accessories, including discounts, warranties, delivery options, and more. The tool also streamlines multiple sections of eOffer/eMod.</p> <p>You will find both interactive training and step-by-step instructions on the Formatted Product Tool in the eOffer/eMod User Guide.</p> <p>Information about the Formatted Product Tool rollout can be found on the MAS Interact group located at: <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules">https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>