<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>eOffer/eMod Release Notes</title><description>The latest release notes for eOffer and eMod.</description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes/releases.rss</link><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 16:07:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 16:07:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Allow the CO/CS to Attach Option Mod Documents Via FSS Online]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that COs/CSs can create an option mod for vendors to then add attachments in eMod. The CO/CS can also receive attachments outside of eMod from the vendor and attach them through FSS Online, and then submit the modification unilaterally.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Authorized Negotiators May Now Access Work in Progress and Contract History]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that all current and future negotiators have the ability to access contract history and any work-in-progress modifications.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Updates to Formatted Products Tool (FPT) for Schedules 58I and 72 Only]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that vendors can now add comments if they do not agree with the standardized XSB data returned while processing an &ldquo;Add Product,&rdquo; &ldquo;Add SIN,&rdquo; or &ldquo;Capture Formatted Pricing&rdquo; modification. The CO can either agree or disagree with the vendor’s request.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Technical Proposal Required for Add SIN Mod Type]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Vendors are now required to enter a technical proposal via the on-screen entry as part of submitting an “Add SIN” modification. If you submitted a technical proposal as part of your offer, then the content you submitted will be prepopulated and presented for your review. If you did not submit a technical proposal as part of your offer, then you will need to address the required elements as part of completing the modification.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Industrial Funding Fee (IFF) POC Field]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that the <em>Industrial Funding Fee POC</em> is now a mandatory POC for all offers, and that multiple entries are permitted. Existing vendors can manage this Point of Contact through a new modification time being introduced.</p> <p>For existing contract holders, this POC will be pre-populated with the information of the person listed as the 72A POC;. You will need to validate and/or update this information if you wish to designate a different individual. In addition, these new POCs may need their own digital certificates in order to access eOffer/eMod.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Formatted Product Tool Process]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The Formatted Product Tool will be rolled out to select schedules over the course of the next few months. If you are have a contract under a participating schedule, you will receive a mass mod for that contract. Upon accepting the mass mod, you will have access to the new process, and will be able to enter detailed pricing information for each of your products and accessories, including discounts, warranties, delivery options, and more. The tool also streamlines multiple sections of eOffer/eMod.</p> <p>You will find both interactive training and step-by-step instructions on the Formatted Product Tool in the <a href="">eOffer/eMod User Guide</a>.</p> <p>For the most up to date information about the Formatted Product Tool rollout, please visit the MAS Interact group located at: <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules">https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capture the Vendor Response(s) for Each Clause in Offers and in Mods]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Visit the new <em>Responding to Solicitation Clauses</em> section of the updated eOffer/eMod user guides.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mass Mod for PSS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that you will no longer see the C SINs, but only their non-C equivalent.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Streamlined Offers and Configurable Year Thresholds]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Qualified contractors will be able to submit an offer without the Pathways to Success Training, the Readiness Assessment, and certain sections of the Technical proposal.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Professional Services Schedule Consolidation]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Since the changes have taken place on October 1st, no action is needed by vendors since the change will be managed via a unilateral MassMod.</p><p>You can learn more about the Professional Services Schedule (PSS) on the <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/professionalservicescategory">Professional Service Category Community</a> on <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/">Interact</a> or the PSS portal page, <a href="http://www.gsa.gov/portal/content/200063">Professional Service Schedule</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Updated Help Links Throughout eOffer/eMod]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>View the new <a href="http://eoffer.gsa.gov/AMSupport/index.html">eOffer/eMod Help Center</a>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Duplicate Manufacturer Part Number Enhancement]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Contract holders should take this opportunity to review and update their price lists for both accuracy and completeness. Any altered Manufacturer Part Numbers should be updated so as to be identical to the numbers issued by the manufacturer.</p><p>Per clauses I-FSS-600 Contract Price Lists and 552.238-71 (Submission and Distribution of Authorized FSS Schedule Price Lists), price lists must be complete, and include all supplies, prices, and terms and conditions awarded under a contractor’s FSS contract. A complete price list means that all awarded base products are listed along with all associated descriptive data (to include MPN).</p><p>Going forward you should ensure that correct manufacturer part numbers are submitted for all products in your price list.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Auto-split for Bundled Instantly Effective Price Reduction Modifications]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>You should be aware that the following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customers)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Requested)</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Technical Proposal Creation in eOffer]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>During the course of 2015, each solicitation in eOffer will include a new section, titled &ldquo;solicitations provisions&rdquo;. In this section, offerors will address provisions specific to each solicitation, and provide written detail about their corporate experience, past performance, and quality control.</p><p>Requirements of each section of the provisions are listed with the corresponding text entry boxes. This ensures consistency and completeness from the vendors. You must respond to all provisions listed in the table, before you may submit your offer.</p><p>The result is a more user-friendly system and standardized eOffer that Contracting Officers can process more efficiently. </p><p>More information on the Solicitation Provisions process can be found in the <em>eOffer Help Center</em>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Price Reduction Modifications Now Take Effect Upon Submission]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customer)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Request)</li></ul><p>In submitting these modifications, you are now required to agree to the following statements:</p><ul><li>This modification is allowed ONLY to reflect price reductions to be applied to the awarded items under my Multiple Award Schedule contract. No other changes can be included, and all other contract terms and conditions remain in full effect.</li><li>Submitted price reduction modifications are effective immediately upon submission.</li><li>I must update my Authorized Federal Supply Schedule Price List as soon as possible to reflect the price reductions described herein.</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
