<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<releases>
    <release>
    <date>2016-08-20</date>
    <changes>
      <change>
        <title>Technical Proposal Required for Add SIN Mod Type</title>
        <number>0</number>
        <system>eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>The addition of a new SIN may impact aspects of the technical proposal. The recently implemented on-screen technical proposal interface was initially deployed as part of the offer process only. This functionality is being expanded to apply to “Add SIN” modifications.</p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Vendors are now required to enter a technical proposal via the on-screen entry as part of submitting an “Add SIN” modification. If you submitted a technical proposal as part of your offer, then the content you submitted will be prepopulated and presented for your review.  If you did not submit a technical proposal as part of your offer, then you will need to address the required elements as part of completing the modification.</p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
      <change>
        <title>Industrial Funding Fee (IFF) POC Field</title>
        <number>1</number>
        <system>eOffer/eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Previously, the Industrial Funding Fee Point of Contact (IFF POC) was only required for offerors completing a subcontracting plan.  </p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Be aware that the <em>Industrial Funding Fee POC</em> is now a mandatory POC for all offers, and that multiple entries are permitted. Existing vendors can add this Point of Contact with a modification.</p>
          <p>Note that this POC will be pre-populated with the information of the person listed as the 72A POC; you will need to validate this information. In addition, these new POCs may need their own digital certificates. </p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>
      <change>
        <title>New Formatted Product Tool Process</title>
        <number>2</number>
        <system>eOffer/eMod</system>
        <type>Update/Enhancement</type>
        <motivation>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>Previously, the process for entering product-related information did not capture the most comprehensive picture of your offer. A process was needed to obtain the most detailed data so that COs could more accurately evaluate offers.</p>]]></description>
        </motivation>
        <effect>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>The Formatted Product Tool will be rolled out to select schedules over the course of the next few months.  Contract holders under affected schedules will receive a mass mod.  If you are part of an affected schedule, you will receive a mass mod.  Upon accepting the mass mod, you will have access to the new process, and will be able to enter detailed pricing information for each of your products and accessories, including discounts, warranties, delivery options, and more. The tool also streamlines multiple sections of eOffer/eMod.</p>
          <p>You will find both interactive training and step-by-step instructions on the Formatted Product Tool in the eOffer/eMod User Guide.</p>
          <p>Information about the Formatted Product Tool rollout can be found on the MAS Interact group located at: <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules">https://interact.gsa.gov/groups/multiple-award-schedules</a>.</p>]]></description>
          <images>            
          </images>
        </effect>
      </change>       
    </changes>
  </release>
</releases>