<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>eOffer/eMod Release Notes</title><description>The latest release notes for eOffer and eMod.</description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes/releases.rss</link><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 18:21:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 18:21:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Technical Proposal Creation in eOffer]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>During the course of 2015, each solicitation in eOffer will include a new section, titled &ldquo;solicitations provisions&rdquo;. In this section, offerors will address provisions specific to each solicitation, and provide written detail about their corporate experience, past performance, and quality control.</p><p>Requirements of each section of the provisions are listed with the corresponding text entry boxes. This ensures consistency and completeness from the vendors. You must respond to all provisions listed in the table, before you may submit your offer.</p><p>The result is a more user-friendly system and standardized eOffer that Contracting Officers can process more efficiently. </p><p>More information on the Solicitation Provisions process can be found in the <em>eOffer Help Center</em>.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Price Reduction Modifications Now Take Effect Upon Submission]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>The following modifications will automatically receive an effective date that is identical to the date of submission:</p><ul><li>Temporary Price Reduction</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (based on Most Favored Customer)</li><li>Permanent Price Reduction (Industry Partner Request)</li></ul><p>In submitting these modifications, you are now required to agree to the following statements:</p><ul><li>This modification is allowed ONLY to reflect price reductions to be applied to the awarded items under my Multiple Award Schedule contract. No other changes can be included, and all other contract terms and conditions remain in full effect.</li><li>Submitted price reduction modifications are effective immediately upon submission.</li><li>I must update my Authorized Federal Supply Schedule Price List as soon as possible to reflect the price reductions described herein.</li></ul><p>Please note, you will still need to submit your price change via SIP/EDI in order for the change to be reflected on Advantage.</p>]]></description><link>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</link><guid>http://www.elucidsolutions.com/projects/OAM/vendor-release-notes#1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>